[♪ epic theme music playing]
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
[Orwyle]
I must see the queen.
[door opens]
Your Grace.
[Rhaenyra gasping]
He is risen.
- Who?
- Aegon!
Sunfyre is alive.
Out!
Sunfyre is dead.
rotting in a wasteland.
[hyperventilating]
- Oh.
- Sit down.
Aegon burned
the Mooton host
at Rook's Rest.
and then flew...
I don't know where.
His supporters have already sent
ravens throughout the realm...
announcing the king's return.
The smallfolk name it
a sign from the gods
that Aegon is ordained to rule.
that he and his dragon
have been resurrected
to reclaim the throne.
At this moment.
mine own subjects
gather outside the Grand Sept.
beseeching the gods
to say who is meant
to rule them.
After all for which
I have fought and suffered!
Rhaenyra.
[sobbing]
[Daemon shushing]
The lesser gods have no say
in what is to come.
We are the blood
of Old Valyria.
You have an absolute power
within your grasp.
You have only to wield it.
Fucking Viserys!
He put me here.
His prophecy has tested me
again and again.
and I have met
its every challenge!
[speaking High Valyrian]
♪
Your Grace.
have plans been laid
for the Sea Snake's rescue?
There will be a rescue?
Your father
will search Tumbleton
for the Sea Snake
once the town
has been reclaimed.
He'll be long dead by then.
- Send me now.
- [scoffs]
You and Addam are needed here
to guard the city.
if indeed these rumors are true
and Sunfyre
was allowed to live.
Corlys is your Hand.
your oldest ally.
I do not wish
your grandsire ill.
but he made his choice.
and we must now
pay its price.
It was your fault.
What?
That Lord Corlys
was out there to be taken.
You do not dare.
It is how you've always
treated those who serve you.
Addam and I have labored
without rest
over countless sorties
in search of your enemies.
only to be repaid
in your anger.
Yes. that is because
your sorties
have yielded nothing.
while my enemies
have been allowed
to muster their strength.
If a person is useful to you.
you wield them.
But if not.
you abandon them
as you have with Rhaena.
And now. she is broken.
like my grandsire.
I would have been justified in
abandoning you after the Gullet.
Perhaps.
But you need my dragon.
Insolent child.
I should not blame you
for it truly.
Insolence runs in your blood.
As your sister
has lately reminded us.
[sighs]
[Alyn]
Good morrow. my lords.
[Maynard]
"Good morrow." indeed.
We've just sailed through
the night from Driftmark.
after learning our Lord Admiral
is hostage to the Hightowers.
The queen has called upon you
to secure King's Landing.
To answer her could mean
our lord's death.
Lord Corlys knew of the risks
of his adventures.
He would want us to appraise
Velaryon honor
as greater than his life.
Who are you to speak
to our lord's desires?
His eldest living son.
And named successor.
Your once and future
Lord of the Tides.
[guard] Open the gates!
[horses whinnying]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
About face!
Forward march!
That...
all of it. is for you.
Remarkable. is it not?
But...
you must be made a knight...
before you can be crowned king.
Kneel.
Daeron Targaryen.
do you swear before the eyes
of gods and men
to defend those
who cannot defend themselves...
- [people clamoring]
- [guard] Everyone inside!
[Ormund]
...to protect all women
and children...
[guard]
Come back here! Back!
[Ormund]
...to obey your captains.
your liege lord...
[guard] Seal the gates!
[Ormund]
...to fight bravely
whenever needed...
and to do such other tasks
- as are laid upon you...
- Steady!
- ...however hard...
- Hoist!
...or humble
or dangerous they may be?
Halt!
I swear it.
Then. rise a knight.
Ser Daeron the Daring.
And light the way.
[Silverwing snarling]
The Queen of Bastards' armies
are at the gates.
And leading them
to the slaughter
will be her uncle.
No. [snaps]
- Her lover.
- [laughing]
No. [snaps]
Her husband.
Daemon fucking Targaryen.
- And his dragon.
- Of course he's got
a fucking dragon!
But he's not gonna use it.
And how do you know?
'Cause his lady wife.
the queen. won't let him.
Rhaenyra's got Daemon
on a short lead.
Like a bitch in a kennel.
Another ale for the dragonlord.
The Rogue Prince
will soon quake
before the mighty and terrible
Lord Ulf the White!
[Elinda] Your Grace.
Y-Your Grace.
is aught amiss?
What is it?
The Princess Helaena.
She still has not taken food.
The maesters
worry for her health.
especially for the babe
in her belly.
Summon Ser Alyn.
I require a full escort
to the Grand Sept.
There. today.
the High Septon
will anoint me
and bless my reign for all
of King's Landing to see.
There will be no doubt who
the gods have chosen to rule.
At once. Your Grace.
Will that be all?
No.
[door opens]
What is this?
Sers.
- Sers!
- [Elinda] My lady.
Beg pardon for the intrusion.
We weren't given much time.
Time for what?
Your passage
has been arranged aboard
the Mermaid's Kiss.
You are to sail
for Pentos at dusk.
I am to inform you
that your services here
are at an end.
[items clattering]
You have served the queen
and the realm most faithfully.
and Her Grace wishes
to extend her gratitude.
[clattering continues]
You will be provided with gold
sufficient for a manse
and servants of your own.
[clattering continues]
Be quick about it.
I-- I do not understand either.
my lady.
[wind swishing]
The hour has passed.
my lady.
I must return you
to your quarters.
[horse nickering]
This way. princess.
[door opens]
Do not trust the queen.
Aegon has returned.
His dragon lives.
Your unborn child
is a hostage.
a prize by which
she can hold power
- over her enemies.
- [guard] Keep moving.
- Enough.
- She will never release you.
[Aemond's voice echoing]
Do you remember?
- [echoed screaming]
- Do you remember?
Help me.
[Alys] Fret not.
You're alive.
Here.
Drink this.
There'll be another in an hour.
She poisoned me.
You have realized
you're alone in this world.
In that. we are together.
[Aemond groaning softly]
But I no longer wish
to suffer it.
Do you?
Why do you care
whether I am alone?
Whether I live or die?
I'm a kinslayer. Alys.
My own brother
is dead by my hand.
I have been damned
for my trespasses
and cursed to suffer.
- You should abandon me.
- [scoffs softly]
Lest you bring mine own fate
upon yourself.
When the dragon Balerion
burned this place.
it was to end
Lord Harren's line.
But his line
was not so easily ended.
A child. a...
a boy...
lived on.
Burned terribly.
but alive.
His mother would have
given anything to save him.
She summoned maesters
from across the Seven Kingdoms.
but to no avail.
So. she turned to older cures.
She uncovered incantations
more ancient than the land.
She treated with things
that lived in the forest.
But none of it could unmake
what dragonfire made.
And when the boy was gone...
she tr-- she tried
to go with him.
And that is when
she learned the cost.
[sniffling]
She discovered then
she was cursed.
To live on...
to remain within the bounds
of the river kings of old...
cursed for sharing
in Harren's avarice.
Stripped of her name.
her title.
her castle.
[sniffling]
And sentenced to serve
every ha'penny lord
who came here to rule it.
That was a hundred years past.
It's a long time
to be alone.
[♪ soft. dramatic music playing]
You must eat. sister.
[door closes]
Think of the babe.
You are thinking
of him now. too?
You're saying it's a boy?
Do you know this?
Look at me.
You cannot think
I would harm you.
Do you think life is nothing
more than not being dead?
[sighs]
Our father
would hate you for this.
And yet he did nothing
to prevent it.
I strove to honor
his philosophy
until I saw that it would be
the realm's undoing.
There is a beetle that emerges
on the cusp of summer.
It has lots of colors.
Blue. gold. purples.
It looks like a turtle.
Have you ever noticed it?
I can't say I have.
You can only find it
in King's Landing.
It sustains itself on the waste
of other creatures.
It's beautiful.
[chuckles softly]
Well. when summer returns.
you will have to show me.
You don't care about it.
You're pretending.
All the things you care about
are ugly.
This place...
is ugly.
[sighs]
You. yourself...
ugly.
Eat.
Or you will force my hand.
No.
No! No!
No! No! No!
Stop! Stop.
[panicked breathing]
[muffled screaming]
[choking]
[coughing]
[guard] Forward march!
[guard shouting indistinctly]
[Addam] Brother.
Will you march
on Tumbleton as well?
No. Today we guard the queen
in her purpose.
Where does she go?
News of Aegon's return has set
the queen on a dark path.
She has grounded Baela
and confined her to the Keep.
Did you know this?
These are dangerous days.
and it is not mine
to question Her Grace.
Why would you?
While our father awaits
the Hightower gallows.
Rhaenyra raises you up
in his place.
A glorious ascent for a bastard.
[guards shouting indistinctly]
I have no ambition
but to discharge my duty.
Be ready!
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[Alyn] Form up!
[guard] Form up!
March!
[soldiers chattering]
[Daeron] Gods.
How will we face them all?
Bravely and pointlessly.
Take your places. boys.
Keep coming. take your places.
Keep coming. Be brave.
Put the boys to the front.
They must be seen.
My lord. Ulf hasn't reported.
and he's not with his dragon.
Take a tithing of men
off each post.
Search the town.
Find him.
[Roxton]
You! With me.
- Something's wrong.
- Yes.
We're all going to die.
No.
With Uncle.
He and Roxton
have some secret plot afoot.
He has kept it even from me.
- [Gwayne] Whatever it was...
- Get away from me!
...it has not appeared
to have come to pass.
Please!
Please. ser.
we don't want to do it.
- I just want to go home
to my mom.
- Don't make us.
[children begging]
I must take wing
against the enemy.
No!
All these men. these boys.
are here for me.
- I cannot let them fight alone.
- For what purpose. boy?
To become another body
amongst Ormund's countless dead?
What are my choices?
I either fight. or I flee.
[sighs]
[dragon bellowing]
Mayhaps there is another.
[soldier] Dragon!
[all shouting]
[Caraxes whistles]
[chuckles]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[Ormund]
Ulf the Dragonrider!
I'm looking for
Ulf the Dragonrider.
- Ulf!
- [Caraxes screeching]
Ulf!
And now. Lord Ormund's boy king
and his faithful squire.
Shut up.
Driftmark lies in ruin.
your legacy in tatters.
But King Daeron. in all
his generosity and wisdom.
can offer a richer future
than the one Rhaenyra
has laid for you.
My honor is all
that remains to me.
Do you really think I would
hawk it for Hightower coin?
[Gwayne] Very well.
The hard road. then.
[bell tolling]
[townsfolk chattering]
[guard] Make way!
Clear the way!
- Move back!
- Get back! Get back!
- Move! Clear the way!
- [people shouting]
- Get back!
- [horse whinnying]
[guards continue shouting]
[bell tolling]
[guard] Get back!
You are my heir now. Joffrey.
and the duty I pass to you
is more than simple rule.
There is a story
that your grandsire told me.
It was told to him
by the Old King.
And I passed it on...
to your brother...
following mine own ascent.
[bellowing]
Tumbleton. my lords!
At long last.
[Oscar Tully]
If it weren't for Cole.
we'd have been here
a fortnight ago.
So easy to forget about him.
Do tell me how he died.
Badly.
[Caraxes whistling]
My prince. my lords.
a Hightower knight approaches.
So? Kill him.
With Lord Corlys.
Hyah.
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[Gwayne]
Prince Daemon.
I am Ser Gwayne Hightower.
Well met.
[Roderick]
Fuck me.
[chuckles]
I've seen more meat
on a butcher's knife.
Can I kill him?
[Gwayne coughs]
You already know Lord Corlys.
Are you well?
I'm well enough.
So. speak.
My cousin Ormund
has taken leave of his senses.
He would rather die
than admit defeat.
And you?
Well. I'm not blind.
I know we will not survive
the day if you attack.
So. as a token of good faith...
- I return your Hand.
- [chains rattling]
[scoffs]
Four fingers of him. at least.
I have come to sue for peace.
- [laughing]
- To plead with you
at the behest
of Daeron Targaryen.
[chuckles] The latest
in your line of false kings.
[Daemon] The war will end
when all the traitors' heads
are mounted on spikes
above the King's Gate...
and not before.
[Gwayne]
Listen to Daeron's entreaty.
Divide the realm.
Let the queen rule
over the Crownlands.
the North.
the Vale. all the lands
watered by the Trident.
and let Daeron
rule from Oldtown.
Oh. please!
Let me kill this milk-suck
southerling cunt.
The realm was once
seven kingdoms.
before the Conqueror.
when we were divided
- but at peace--
- Stop!
My good Lord Hand.
I thought the Hightowers
might have cut off
your tongue as well.
Hightower is not wrong.
There are great houses
who still hold to the precedent
set by the Great Council
that a woman cannot rule.
It was your wife
who was passed over. Corlys.
Rhaenyra seized the throne
with a horde of dragons.
Her rule is now unassailable.
The queen
has many dragons. yes.
but the great houses hesitate.
Her subjects do not feel safe.
nor should they.
Aemond and Vhagar
remain at large.
[chain rattling]
Give Prince Daeron Oldtown.
Name him Lord Paramount
of the Reach.
Daeron will never be king.
but he and his dragon
can be wardens of the South.
That wasn't what I was offering.
Wed Daeron to Rhaena.
Seal the breach
between your houses.
With the combined will
of King's Landing.
the Reach. the North.
the Riverlands.
and the Vale. Rhaenyra
can quickly bring the West
and the Stormlands to heel.
And what will
the usurper Aegon say
when he hears of this pact?
He now scuttles about somewhere
on his crippled dragon.
half-cooked.
but still fit to rule.
Or so he thinks.
Was that news?
It is so tragic to see
brother set against brother.
Aegon and Aemond
would be common enemies
of this new alliance.
Alliance?
I never took you for a traitor.
Corlys. and worse. a craven.
What price has the boy king
offered for your fealty?
Peace.
Two paths
diverge before you. Daemon.
but both lead to the same end.
Rhaenyra sitting the Iron Throne
ruling the Seven Kingdoms.
All that remains
for you to decide...
is what you want
from this war.
Victory?
Or a mountain
of dead Hightowers?
What do you think?
You would callously cast away
the lives of thou--
[choking]
No one will rule but Rhaenyra.
the ordained
Queen of the Andals.
of the First Men.
of beggars and thieves
and cowards like you.
A new Valyria
will rise from the ashes
of her usurper half-brothers
and of the Hightowers
of Oldtown.
Now. you came to me
under a banner of peace.
so I will give you the choice.
Die here.
or behind those walls.
like the rodent you are.
[Gwayne coughing]
Lord Corlys is my prisoner.
Hightower may return
to alert his cousin
- to our imminent coming.
- Get up! Get up! [shouting]
[Daemon]
Bring the ladders and the rams
and form up to march.
The next man
to stall on this attack
will be tied to the front
of my fucking horse!
[breathing heavily]
- [distant dragon screeching]
- [gasps]
[dragon wings flapping]
[faint screeching]
- [dragon screeching]
- [wings flapping]
[dragon screeching]
- [dragon snarling]
[wheezing]
[chittering]
[breathing heavily]
It cannot be.
You are dead.
[smacking]
I'm alive!
Imbecile.
Brother. Brother.
I beg for your forgiveness.
[giggling]
[laughing]
Forgiveness?
I should split you in half.
Hm?
I should have Sunfyre
burn you alive.
Mm. but slowly.
So I can see your skin...
peel and blister.
You kinslayer.
[whispering]
You usurper.
You cunt!
No.
No. no. no. no. no. no. no!
I was supposed to enjoy this.
What's wrong with you?
Fight me!
[sighs]
I coveted what you had
and judged you unsuited
for the crown.
Oh.
[Sunfyre chittering]
I tried to kill you
to take your place.
You'd be right
to sentence me to die.
Fuck you.
Get up.
We're going to Tumbleton.
My prince cannot.
His dragon abandoned him.
- Who's she?
- My betrothed.
Do you know what's happening
out there?
[softly] No?
Rhaenyra declared me dead.
And after you disappeared.
that little twat Daeron
decided he should be king.
So. here's what
we're going to do.
We're going to find Vhagar.
fly to Tumbleton.
and put Daeron
and that shitheel
Ormund in line.
And then. we're all going
to march on King's Landing
under my banner.
And maybe. when Rhaenyra's
head is on a spike...
and I'm back
on the Iron Throne...
- Aemond.
- [Aegon shushing]
Maybe then...
I'll forgive you...
for trying to fucking kill me.
[Oscar]
Aside from the main gate.
there's one other way in.
A disused postern
on the northeast side.
They've raised
wooden battlements
but the defenses
are incomplete.
so there are vulnerable areas.
particularly the walls
to the southeast.
Simple enough.
I will burn the battlements
over the main gate.
Once they're
clear of resistance.
our van will lead the attack
with Caraxes for cover.
Ulf and Silverwing
will guard the rear.
Rhaenyra's banners will fly
above the holdfast
by nightfall.
Take every care to preserve
the town and its people.
The realm is watching.
The queen's moral standing
must remain absolute.
Sounds boring.
My prince.
My lords.
Movement at the walls.
The enemy has fortified
their numbers with children.
[softly] Gods.
- How many?
- Scores.
All along the battlements.
And that's just
what I could see.
[Oscar]
He's testing you. my prince.
daring you
to use your dragon.
The spineless cunt.
Lord Roderick. are you still
prepared to die for our queen?
Can't fucking wait.
Take your greybeards
over the walls.
overwhelm them with
your northern fighting spirit
and open the gate
from within.
But you are not to die
until you open the gate.
Aye. gate open. then die.
Lord Oscar will lead the flank
as planned.
Ser Garibald has the reserve.
The center is mine.
[♪ dramatic music playing]
This is the House of the Seven.
No arms are to cross
its threshold.
The people
of King's Landing gather.
seeking to know
who is ordained to lead them.
You will give them their answer
by anointing me
for all to see.
I have already told you
that such is impossible.
And now. after Aegon
and his dragon
have been resurrected.
there could be no clearer sign
of whom the gods
have chosen to rule. princess.
I am queen.
The old man forgets.
I wear my father's crown
and sit his throne...
with six dragons at my heel.
You will not deny me
my right a second time.
You may have six dragons.
but I have a Seven-faced god.
I could not possibly
oppose their will.
Then. you name yourself
a traitor.
I am the High Septon
of the Faith.
To harm me is to declare war
upon the Starry Sept.
To damn your soul to the deepest
of the Seven Hells.
You are the blood
of Old Valyria.
You answer
to higher gods than his.
To them. this house...
is an empty work
of brick and stone.
We stand on sacred ground.
- A place of refuge!
- [people gasping]
[grunting. gasping]
[doors close]
[flag flapping softly]
Before his death...
my father.
Viserys the Peaceful...
named me his heir.
Not in secret.
but in ceremony.
Hundreds of lords traveled
hundreds of leagues
to swear fealty to me
before gods and men.
But my rule
was already ordained.
It was prophesied...
long before even Viserys
was born.
It began with the Doom...
when fire and hell erupted
to destroy Old Valyria
and her people.
I need Ulf the Dragonrider!
In there. Find him!
[Rhaenyra]
Only the Targaryens survived.
Where is he?
My family alone were spared.
[people shouting]
The gods summoned my ancestor.
Aegon the Conqueror...
to the Seven Kingdoms
to unite a fractured realm
beneath one banner
of black and red.
They named him
Protector of the World of Men.
His duty. to shield it...
from an ancient
and sinister darkness
that looms in the far North...
beyond the Wall.
beyond the lands of winter.
And only the might of dragons
can stand against it.
The Conqueror passed
this sacred charge
to his chosen descendants.
to the Old King. Jaehaerys.
then to my father.
then to me.
The Hightower line
cannot fulfill this prophecy.
If your world is to survive...
I must light the way.
Because I am
the Shield of the People.
I am Rhaenyra the Chosen.
♪
Lords. knights.
savages. and cutthroats!
[army laughing]
Whether you live or die today...
you will be remembered
in the histories
as those who began
the Hightowers' end!
Grant no mercy!
Give no quarter.
I don't want the best of you.
I want the worst!
- [army shouting]
- [swords and shields clanging]
[drums banging]
[horse whinnying]
[shouting continues]
Go now...
and kill them.
[swords and shields
continue clanging]
[horn blowing]
[shouting]
[shouting continues]
[drums continue banging]
Right. lads!
- Blades out!
- [swords unsheathing]
Bellies in!
[all shout]
[drums continue banging]
[rhythmic shouting
and banging]
- [distant drums banging]
- [Caraxes whistling]
[children whimpering]
[urine trickling]
[children sobbing]
[retching]
[distant rhythmic banging
intensifying]
Siege engines. make ready!
Archers. draw.
- [bows creaking]
- Draw. draw. draw!
[guard] Good aim. lads!
[distant rhythmic banging
continues]
[townspeople whimpering
and sobbing]
[army shouting]
[shouting]
[shouting and banging stop]
Come on. then!
Send your fucking arrows.
you boy-touching cunts!
[arrows thwacking]
- [growling]
- [army shouting]
[all growling and shouting]
Loose!
[army shouting]
[horse whinnying]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[Roxton] My lord.
There is no sign or word
of Ulf anywhere.
- He's deserted.
- My lord.
The battle has begun.
- You don't say?
- Yes. my lord.
It appears Daemon Targaryen
did not accept
King Daeron's terms.
Terms?
Speak!
King Daeron.
he sent Ser Gwayne
to treat with the enemy
under a banner of peace.
He freed the Sea Snake.
my lord. as part of the bargain.
[Roxton]
Continue the search.
Find Ulf the Dragonrider.
[soldiers shouting]
Where is the prince?
The king?
- [army shouting]
- [arrows whizzing]
Ladders! The ladders!
[thud]
Oil!
[screaming]
- [screaming]
- [sizzling]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
Advance!
South wall!
[shouting]
[screaming]
[soft thud]
[Hightower captain] Arrows!
Light the trenches!
[soldiers screaming]
Your Grace. I cannot find
Ser Ulf the White.
What do you mean.
you cannot find him?
He has a very large dragon.
Begging pardon. Your Grace.
He is not with his dragon.
[arrow thwacking]
Turret!
[soldiers shouting]
[Roxton] Stop!
Find that fucking gate. lads!
Take them.
- [knight] Draw swords!
- [laughing]
- [Roderick] Kill them!
- Forward!
- [shouting]
- [swords clanging]
[dragon bellowing]
Is that Hugh Hammer's dragon?
Hugh is meant to be guarding
King's Landing.
Learn why he's here.
[♪ dramatic music playing]
Center! Form on me!
Caraxes!
[heavy footfall]
[horses whinnying]
- At ready!
- Hold your positions!
Dragon!
Bring down the rider!
[arrows whizzing]
Dracarys!
[soldiers screaming]
Move! Get down there!
- Through the doors!
- [children crying]
Come on!
Get out of the way!
Move!
- [Caraxes screeching]
- [children screaming]
Dracarys!
[screeching]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
Forward!
[horses whinnying]
[arrows whizzing]
[horse whinnying]
[shouting]
[whinnying]
[soldiers shouting]
[horn blowing]
[soldier]
To the main gates!
That's the gates
open then. lads.
- And we're still fucking alive.
- [soldiers shouting]
Find me that boy king.
Go now!
I want Lord Hightower.
[light snoring]
[quick footsteps approaching]
[banging]
- [soldier gagging]
- Get him out!
[groaning]
- Get up!
- You worthless sot!
All you had to do was sit
on your fucking dragon!
They're inside the walls!
You useless baseborn stump!
You may have cost us everything.
Now. get back on that beast.
and do as you've been told!
[townspeople screaming]
[gasps]
Ormund Hightower!
[sword stabbing]
[Hugh]
Kat. where are you?
Kat!
Ormund Hightower!
[Roxton] Kinslayer!
Babe killer.
Heathen!
[bellowing]
Ser Ulf. I have orders
from Prince Daemon
to make certain that you
and your dragon are at the--
[exclaiming]
- [dragon snarling]
- Daeron!
Your parlay failed.
Daemon's overwhelmed the city.
You will die.
But I won't be remembered
a craven.
I have fought
beside other brave men
who believed that death
was the only path to glory.
Do not die for Ormund's vanity.
[Tessarion snarling]
My boy.
My boy. please.
Please!
- [Tessarion bellowing]
- Stay back.
[panting]
[Tessarion snarling]
[whispering]
Stay back.
You'll have to come
through me then.
[Tessarion screeching]
[army cheering]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[Ulf]
Dracarys!
[people screaming]
[dragon screeching]
[Roxton] There you are.
[shouting]
[Silverwing bellowing]
There's Ormund's piece
on the board.
Perhaps we'll survive the day.
- [Silverwing bellowing]
- Clear a path!
[screaming]
[growling]
[grunting. shouting]
[shouting]
[Silverwing bellowing]
- [blade stabbing]
- [grunting]
[screaming]
- [retching]
- [Roderick shouting]
[screaming]
That's a proper fucking.
By the North.
[Silverwing roaring]
Fuck you. too.
- [laughing]
- No. No!
[screaming]
Move! Find cover!
[Silverwing bellowing]
[muffled rumbling]
[muffled rumbling continues]
[muffled screeching]
[muffled] Where are you?!
[muffled clanging]
[♪ soft. somber music playing]
[muffled hoofbeats]
[woman sobbing]
[muffled rumbling continues]
[♪ soft. somber music
continues playing]
[muffled rumbling continues]
[♪ soft. somber music
continues playing]
[shouting]
Ulf has turned.
The town is lost.
We are leaving.
[dragon screeching]
♪
[♪ soft. somber music
continues playing]
♪
[weakly] Daeron.
[coughing]
[gasping] Daeron.
[♪ soft. somber music
continues playing]
Kat. Kat!
[screaming]
[♪ somber music
continues playing]
[Elinda] My queen!
[♪ somber music
continues playing]
♪
[butterfly wings flapping]
[♪ music ends]
[wind whistling]
[♪ soft. dramatic music playing]
[♪ music intensifying]
[♪ music fades]
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm